Devansh Shrivastava

Computer Science & Engineering



🗹 devanshshrivastava07@gmail.com 🛭 📊 /devansh0331





(n) /devansh0331

Personal Profile

I'm a React Js and Web Development Enthusiast. Currently pursuing my B.Tech in Computer Science and Engineering from Bhilai Institute of Technology, Durg. I am at ease in Node.js, React.js, Express.js, Bootstrap, Django. I have experience in various events managing technical and non-technical domains.

Projects

Antidote - Close to you 🔗

A website that schedules appointments with the preferable doctor for the respective disease. ReactJS, Bootstrap, Firebase, Web Scrapping

Users Credentials 🔗

Contact us page with Sign up and Login features. ReactJS, Firebase

News Monk 🔗

News website that presents real-time news, driven by APIs.

ReactJS

To-Do List 🔗

Frontend website of a To-Do List application ReactJS

Experience

March 2023-Present

TEDxBITD 2023

Technical Team Member

Nov 2022 - March 2023

Hult Prize, On-Campus, BITD 2023

Marketing Team Member

Sept 2022 - Present

TechnoHub. BITD

Team Member

Sept 2022 - Present

Public Speaking Club, BITD

Social Media Team Member

Education

2021-Present

Bhilai Institute of Technology, Durg

8.7 CPI - 3rd sem

2020 - 21

St. Francis Senior Secondary School, Bilaspur

Class 12 - 94.4 %

2018 - 19

St. Francis Senior Secondary School, Bilaspur

Class 10 - 84.8 %

Certification

Python 3.4.3 Training Completion 🔗

Skills

- ReactJS
- Bootstrap
- Firebase
- Django
- NodeJS

Interests

- Football
- Indian Mythology